Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office. Information Center Records, 1901-2005 and undated RL.11121
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 2018 Additions, 1901-2006 and undated; 1
  - Numbered Research Reports, 1919-1988 and undated; 10
    - X7.1-34-ABC. The Flour Market, 1978 (Box R36)
    - X7.1-34.1-A. German Market for Alcoholic Beverages, 1978 (Box R36)
    - X7.1-35-ABC. Consumer Reaction to Jewel (Food Stores) Generic Products, 1978 (Box R36)
    - X7.1-36-A. U.S. Soup Market, 1979 (Box R36)
    - X7.1-37-A. U.S. Coffee Market, 1978 (Box R36)
    - X7.1-38-A. U.S. Tea Market, 1978 (Box R37)
    - X7.1-39-AB. Consumer Reaction to Jewel (Food Stores) Generic Products, 1978; 2 folders (Box R37)
    - X7.1-40-A. Unbranded Food Product Study, 1979; 4 folders (Box R37)
    - X7.1-41-A. History of Michelob, 1978 (Box R38)
    - X7.1-41.1-ABC. Consumer Reaction to Jewel (Food Stores) Generic Products, undated (Box R38)
    - X7.1-42-ABC. Consumer Reaction to Jewel (Food Stores) Generic Products, undated (Box R38)
    - X7.1-44-A. U.S. Coffee Market, 1980; 3 folders (Box R38)
    - X7.1-45-A. Brand Utility Yardstick, 1979; 2 folders (Box R38)
    - X7.1-46-AB. Changing Environment for Food Marketing in the 1980s (Box R39)
    - X7.1-47-ABC. Consumer Reaction to Jewel (Food Stores) Generic Products, 1981 (Box R39)
    - X7.1-47.01-A. What We Know About Breakfast, 1981 (Box R39)
    - X7.1-47.1-A. BUY (Brand Utility Yardstick) Study, 1981 (Box R39)
    - X7.1-48-A. U.S. Coffee Market, 1981 (Box R39)
    - X7.1-48.1-AB. Retailing Trends in Product Marketing, 1981 (Box R39)
    - X7.1-48.11-A. Overview of the Service Deli Market, 1981 (Box R39)
    - X7.1-49-A. U.S. Distilled Spirits Market, 1981 (Box R39)
    - X7.1-50-A. U.S. Wine Market, 1981 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-50.1-A. U.S. Beer Market, 1981; 2 folders (Box R40)
    - X7.1-52-A. Generics, undated (Box R40)
    - X7.1-53-ABC. The Salad Bar, 1982 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-54-A. Brand Utility Yardstick, 1982 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-55-ABC. Brand Utility Yardstick, 1982 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-57-ABC. Investigation of "Light" Products, 1983 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-57.1-A. The Breakfast Experience, 1983 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-57.2-A. Hendry Analysis of the Fast Food Industry, 1983 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-58-A. Attitudes and Behaviors Toward Salt and Sugar, 1983 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-59-A Vol. 1. Consumer Trends Affecting the Future of Food Marketing, 1983 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-59-A Vol. 2. Thought for Food, 1983 (Box R40)
    - X7.1-60-A. EBD (pesticide) Contamination, 1984 (Box R41)
    - X7.1-61-AB. U.S. Frozen Food Industry, undated (Box R41)
    - X7.1-62-A. Bread Category Analysis, 1985 (Box R41)
    - X7.1-63-AB. Beverage Industry Factbook, 1986 (Box R41)
    - X7.1-64-AB. Life's Little Luxuries: The Gourmetization of Everyday Products, 1985 (Box R41)
    - X7.1-65-A. U.S. Beer Market, 1985; 2 folders (Box R41)
    - X7.2-1-ABC. Bird Food Market, 1960 (Box R41)
    - X7.2-2-A. Pet Food Market in the U.S., 1984; 2 folders (Box R41)
    - X7.3-.1-A. New Product Recommendation in the Proprietary Drug Field, 1965 (Box R41)
    - X7.3-.2-A. New Product Proposal: Proprietary Multiple Vitamin, 1960 (Box R41)
    - X7.3-.3-A. Hair Preparation Market in the U. S., 1966 (Box R42)
    - X7.3-1-A. Effervescent Analgesics, 1970 (Box R42)
    - X7.3-1.1-A. Dentifrice Market, 1972 (Box R42)
    - X7.3-1.2-A. Deodorant Market, 1972 (Box R42)
    - X7.3-2-A. Study of the Dentifrice Market, 1973 (Box R42)
    - X7.3-3-A. Cosmetics and Toiletries, 1982; 4 folders (Box R42)
    - X7.3-3-A. Cosmetics and Toiletries, 1982 (Box R43)
    - X7.4-.1-A. Questionnaire Summary, 1970 (Box R43)
    - X7.4-1-ABC. Toy Industry Summary, 1970 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-.1-A. Lawn and Garden Products Market, 1963 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-.2-A. Consumer Reaction to "Omnibus" Advertisement Describing Charcoal Filtration of the "Gas Phase" (Lark Cigarettes), 1968 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-.3-A. Women's Reactions to Three Lark Advertisements, 1968 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-.4-A. Consumer Response to Lark Print Advertisements, 1968 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-.5-A. Consumer Response to Lark Advertisements, 1968 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-.6-A. Consumer Response to Lark Print Advertisements, 1968 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-.7-A. Color Television Purchase Decision Study, 1969 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-.8-A. Automatic Toilet Bowl Cleaner Product Test, 1969 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-1-ABC. Discussion of Fashion and Color Relative to Major Appliances and Housewares, 1971 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-2-ABC. Consumer Response to Advertisements for Gas Heating and Air Conditioning, 1971 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-2.1-A. Lux Dishwashing Detergent Telephone Survey, 1971 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-2.2-A. Lux Presentation, 1971 (Box R43)
    - X7.5-3-ABC. Cellulosics, 1971 (Box R44)
    - X7.5-4-A. Effect of Ecological Considerations on Attitudes Toward Fur Types, 1973 (Box R44)
    - X7.5-4.2-A. Questionnaire: Contact Lenses, 1980 (Box R44)
    - X7.5-5-A. U.S. Jeans Market, 1981 (Box R44)
    - X7.5-6-A. White Goods Industry, 1981 (Box R44)
    - X7.5-7-A. Vacuum Cleaner Industry, 1982 (Box R44)
    - X7.5-7.1-A. Better Sleep Council Consumer Studies, 1983 (Box R44)
    - X7.5-8-ABC. Consumer Attitudes Toward Lawns and Lawn Mowers, 1983 (Box R44)
    - X8-8. A Few Basic Facts About JWT, 1945 (Box R44)
    - X8-8.1-ABC. Manual of Style, 1956 (Box R44)
    - X8-9-A. Manual of Style, 1959 (Box R44)
    - X8-10. Consumer Panel, undated (Box R44)
    - X8-11-AB. Analysis of Consumer Purchase Panel, 1955 (Box R45)
    - X8-12-ABC. The Research Function, 1959 (Box R45)
    - X8-13-A. Statements of Research Philosophy, 1961 (Box R45)
    - X8-14. Traffic Procedures, 1961 (Box R45)
    - X8-14.1-ABC. Policy Statement Prepared for JWT Chicago Research Staff, 1961 (Box R45)
    - X8-15-ABC. Memo to Account Service Personnel, 1961 (Box R45)
    - X8-16-ABC. History of JWT Chicago, 1963 (Box R45)
    - X8-17-AB. Introduction to Marketing Research, 1963 (Box R45)
    - X8-18-ABC. Standards for Report Writing, 1963; 2 folders (Box R45)
    - X8-19-ABC. Group Interviewing at JWT Chicago, 1964 (Box R45)
    - X8-19.1. Account Research Manager, 1965 (Box R45)
    - X8-20. Programmed Advertising, 1965 (Box R45)
    - X8-20.1-A. JWT Creative Development Program, 1966 (Box R45)
    - X8-21-ABC. JWT Chicago Image Study, 1968 (Box R45)
    - X8-22-A. 1974 Managers Meeting, 1969 (Box R45)
    - X8-23-ABC. Employee Attitude Survey, 1969 (Box R46)
    - X8-23.1-ABC. Employee Attitude Survey, 1969 (Box R46)
    - X8-25-A. Computerization at JWT, 1970; 2 folders (Box R46)
    - X8-26-A. Development of an Industrial/Business Marketing Division for JWT, 1970 (Box R46)
    - X8-27-ABCD. Study of the Reputation of JWT, 1969 (Box R46)
    - X8-28-ABC. Research and Planning Department Description, undated (Box R46)
    - X8-28.1-A. JWT Profit Planning Guide, 1969 (Box R46)
    - X8-28.2-ABC. Competitive Advertising, 1971 (Box R46)
    - X8-29-ABC. On Preparing a Research Proposal, 1971 (Box R46)
    - X8-30-ABC. Proposal to Market the Consumer Research Center, 1971 (Box R46)
    - X8-31-ABC. Research Guidelines, 1971 (Box R46)
    - X8-31.1-A. Testing Advertising, 1971 (Box R47)
    - X8-32-ABC. Proposal to Market the Information Center Service "Source", 1972 (Box R47)
    - X8-33-ABC. Review of JWT Custom Advertising Research System, 1974 (Box R47)
    - X8-33.1-A. Harris Advertising Agency Study, 1976 (Box R47)
    - X8-34-A. JWT Research Conference, 1975; 2 folders (Box R47)
    - X8-35-ABC. JWTrend Internal Evaluation Study, 1976 (Box R47)
    - X8-36-AB. JWT Western Division Managerial Feedback and Career Development Program, undated (Box R47)
    - X8-36.5-AB. JWT Research Conference, 1977; 2 folders (Box R47)
    - X8-37-ABC. Annual Personnel Report, 1977 (Box R47)
    - X8-38-A. Practical Use of Research in Marketing, 1978 (Box R47)
    - X8-40-AB. Annual Personnel Report, 1978 (Box R47)
    - X8-40.1-A. Communicating Leadership, 1979 (Box R47)
    - X8-41-A. Three Year Personnel Review (1976-1979), 1980 (Box R48)
    - X8-42-AB. Assessment of Account Structure, 1980 (Box R48)
    - X8-43-ABC. Guide to Research Methods and Terminology, 1980 (Box R48)
    - X8-44-ABC. Information Resources Inventory, 1980 (Box R48)
    - X8-45-A. Professional Development Handbook, undated; 2 folders (Box R48)
    - X8-46-A. Chicago AMA Advanced Statistics Course, 1981 (Box R48)
    - X8-47-A. JWT Western Division Managerial Feedback and Career Development Program, undated (Box R48)
    - X8-48-ABC. Factbook on the Need for Child Care in the 1980s, 1982 (Box R48)
    - X8-49-ABC. Advertising Agency Attitude Study, 1982 (Box R48)
    - X8-50-A. Colin Dawkins, Ain't It Hell on a Windy Day, undated; 3 folders (Box R49)
    - X8-50.1-A. Cableshop Research Program, undated (Box R49)
    - X8-51-AB. Overview of the Research and Planning Department, 1982 (Box R49)
    - X8-52-A. "Response", 1982 (Box R49)
    - X8-52.1-A. Cableshop Monthly Tracking Research, 1982 (Box R49)
    - X8-52.2-A. Cableshop Pilot Test Review, 1982 (Box R49)
    - X8-52.3-A. Cableshop Monthly Tracking Research, 1982 (Box R49)
    - X8-53-A. JWT Chicago Growth Force, 1982 (Box R49)
    - X8-53.1-A. Cableshop Monthly Tracking Research, 1982 (Box R49)
    - X8-54-ABC. Guide to Written Communications, 1982 (Box R50)
    - X8-55-A. Cableshop Pilot Test Review, 1983 (Box R50)
    - X8-58-A. JWT Share of Market, 1984 (Box R50)
    - X8-59-A. JWT Office Plan, 1985 (Box R50)
    - X8-60-A. JWT Office Plan, 1986 (Box R50)
    - X8.1-1-10. Application of Operations Research Solutions to Advertising Agency Problems, 1963 (Box R50)
    - X8.1-2-ABC. Possible Applications of Family Status/Income Group Concept in Advertising Planning for Consumer Products, 1963 (Box R50)
    - X8.1-3. Possible Applications of 9-Cell Concept in Advertising Planning for Consumer Products, 1964 (Box R50)
    - X8.1-4-ABC. Search for the Best Prospects, 1964 (Box R50)
    - X8.1-5-ABC. Mechanized Media Analysis, 1965 (Box R50)
    - X8.1-6-ABC. System for Finding Out Quickly Who's Watching and Who's Buying, 1967 (Box R50)
    - X8.2-1-ABC. Public Reaction to Illinois Department of Mental Health Advertisements, 1968 (Box R50)
    - X8.2-2-AB. Communications Plan for Monitor Research and Recovery Foundation, 1975 (Box R51)
    - X8.2-3-ABC. Red Cross Blood Donor Survey, 1978 (Box R51)
    - X8.2-4-ABC. Red Cross Blood Donor Inquiry, 1978 (Box R51)
    - X8.2-5-ABC. Communications Test: Crusade of Mercy Film "79 Seconds", 1979 (Box R51)
    - X8.2-6-ABC. Alexian Brothers Alcoholic Treatment Program, 1978 (Box R51)
    - X8.2-7-ABC. Crusade of Mercy Commercial Test, 1979 (Box R51)
    - X8.2-8-ABC. Crusade of Mercy Film Study, 1979 (Box R51)
    - X8.2-10-A. Crusade of Mercy Study, 1980 (Box R51)
    - X8.21-1-ABC. Logo for Chicago Boy Scouts, 1973 (Box R51)
    - X8.3-1. Improvement in the Use of Audiovisual Aids, 1968 (Box R51)
    - X8.4-1-ABC. Stimulator Presentations, 1973 (Box R51)
    - X8.4-2-A. How to Make Client Presentations More Effective [VHS] (removed to JWT Chicago Office Information Center Audiovisual Materials series), 1984 (Box R51)
    - X8.4-3-AB. Judging Creative Effectively [VHS and Umatic] (removed to JWT Chicago Office Information Center Audiovisual Materials series), 1984; 3 folders (Box R51)
    - X8.4-4-A. International Advertising Reel [Umatic] (removed to JWT Chicago Office Information Center Audiovisual Materials series), 1984 (Box R51)
    - X8.5-1-ABC. JWT Chicago Approach to Planning Effective Advertising, 1975 (Box R51)
    - X8.5-1.1-A. JWT T-Plan, 1975 (Box R51)
    - X8.5-2-ABC. JWT T-Plan, 1975 (Box R51)
    - X8.5-3-A. JWT Planning Record, undated (Box R52)
    - X8.5-4-ABC. Management Review System and T-Plan, 1976 (Box R52)
    - X8.5-4.1-A. Industrial T-Plan, 1975 (Box R52)
    - X8.5-5-ABC. JWT T-Plan, 1976 (Box R52)
    - X8.5-6-ABC. JWT T-Plan, 1977 (Box R52)
    - X8.5-7. JWT T-Plan, 1980 (Box R52)
    - X8.5-8-ABC/A. JWT T-Plan, 1980 (Box R52)
    - X8.5-9-AB. JWT T-Plan, 1980; 2 folders (Box R52)
    - X9-2. Women and Published Cooking Materials, 1956 (Box R52)
    - X9-3-A. American Bankers Association Motivation Study, 1957 (Box R52)
    - X9-4-ABC. 1964 World's Fair, 1960 (Box R52)
    - X9-6-A. Mass Housing in the U.S., 1960 (Box R52)
    - X9-9-A. Overseas Airlines Awareness and Image Study, 1966 (Box R52)
    - X9-15.1-A. Greyhound Corporation, 1969 (Box R52)
    - X9-15.2-A. McDonald's Marketing Analysis, 1969 (Box R53)
    - X9-15.3-A. Safeway Stores, 1970 (Box R53)
    - X9-16-A. Bank Questionnaire Results, 1972 (Box R53)
    - X9-17-A. Primetime Soap Trends 1980-1984, 1985 (Box R53)
    - X9-18-A. Diet Center, 1983 (Box R53)
    - X9-19-A. Fitness Factbook, 1986 (Box R53)
    - X9.5-15.1. American Road Builders Association, 1960 (Box R53)
    - X9.5-16-ABC. Study of Whirlpool Brand Image, 1960 (Box R53)
    - X9.5-16.1-ABC. Interviews with Appliance Dealers, 1960 (Box R53)
    - X9.5-16.2-ABC. Whirlpool Principle, 1962 (Box R53)
    - X9.5-16.3. Analysis of Midwest Major Appliance Manufacturers, 1961 (Box R53)
    - X9.5-17. Presentation to Sunkist Growers, 1960 (Box R53)
    - X9.5-18. Consumer Electronics Factbook, 1959 (Box R53)
    - X9.5-19. Wilson Sporting Goods, 1960; 2 folders (Box R54)
    - X9.5-19.1-ABC. Current Attitudes Toward Pens, 1960 (Box R54)
    - X9.5-20-ABC. New Era Potato Chips, 1961 (Box R54)
    - X9.5-20.1-ABC. New Era Potato Chips, 1961 (Box R54)
    - X9.5-20.2. Snack Market Fact Book, undated (Box R54)
    - X9.5-20.3-ABC. Survey of Potato Chip Brand Positions, 1963 (Box R54)
    - X9.5-21-ABC. Attitudes Toward Moving Van Lines, 1961 (Box R54)
    - X9.5-22. Discussion on Long Distance Moving, 1961 (Box R54)
    - X9.5-23. Allied Van Lines Fact Book, 1961; 2 folders (Box R54)
    - X9.5-24. Shaeffer Pen Presentation, 1966 (Box R54)
    - X9.5-25. General Mills Fact Book, 1962 (Box R54)
    - X9.5-25. General Mills Fact Book, 1962 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-26-ABC. Water and Water Softeners, 1962 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-27-ABC. Water and Water Softeners, 1962 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-28. Container Corporation Fact Book, 1962 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-29-A. Illinois Bell Telephone, 1962 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-29.1-ABC. Illinois Bell Telephone, 1962 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-30-ABC. Attitudes Toward Food Vending, 1962 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-30.1. Automatic Canteen Company Fact Book, 1963 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-31-ABC. Regional Brewers, 1962 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-32. Sunbeam (appliance) Fact Book, 1963 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-33. Illinois Bell Telephone, 1961 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-34-ABC. Attitudes of Users and Non-Users of Evaporated Milk, 1963 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-34.1-ABC. Study on the Use of Evaporated Milk, 1963 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-34.2-ABC. Canned Evaporated Milk, 1963 (Box R55)
    - X9.5-35. Westclox Fact Book, undated (Box R56)
    - X9.5-36-ABC. Supreme "Kitchen Rich" Cookies, 1963 (Box R56)
    - X9.5-37. Biscuit Industry Fact book, 1962 (Box R56)
    - X9.5-38-AB. Concepts of Wrist Watches, 1964 (Box R56)
    - X9.5-38.01-ABC. Encyclopedia Britannica, 1964 (Box R56)
    - X9.5-38.1-AB. Encyclopedia Britannica, 1964 (Box R56)
    - X9.5-38.2-A. Pizza Hut, 1976; 2 folders (Box R56)
    - X9.5-39-ABC. Research on Encyclopedias, 1964 (Box R56)
    - X9.5-40-ABC. Encyclopedia Britannica, 1964 (Box R56)
    - X9.5-40.1. Encyclopedia Study, undated (Box R56)
    - X9.5-41-C. Encyclopedia Britannica, 1964 (Box R56)
    - X9.5-41.1-AB. Lewis-Howe (Tums) Antacid Market Report, undated (Box R56)
    - X9.5-41.1-AB. Lewis-Howe (Tums) Antacid Market Report, undated (Box R57)
    - X9.5-42-ABC. Lawn Boy Power Mowers Marketing Plan, undated (Box R57)
    - X9.5-43. Characteristics of Toy Advertising, 1965 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-44-ABC. Whitman Company (Toys) Marketing Plan, 1965 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-45-ABC. Interstate Moving Industry and North American Van Lines, 1965 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-46-ABC. Concepts About and Attitudes Toward Orange Juice, 1965 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-46.1. Market and Consumer Data: Citrus Products, 1966 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-47-ABC. Consumer Concept of Frozen Orange Juice Concentrate Prices in Chicago, 1965 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-50-ABC. Dr. Scholl's Products and Advertising, 1966 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-51-ABC. The Writing Instrument Industry, 1966 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-51.1. Presentation for W.A. Shaeffer Pen Company, 1966 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-52-ABCDE. Advertising and Marketing Plan--Cook Chemical Company, 1966 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-52.1. Cook Chemical: Pesticide Industry Study, 1967 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-53-ABC. Background and Data on Selected Brewers, 1966 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-53.1. Chicago Daily News: New Business, 1966 (Box R57)
    - X9.5-56-ABC. Current Pen Advertising, 1967 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-57-ABC. Compilation of Data on the Writing Instrument Industry, 1967 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-58-ABC. Trade Attitudes Toward the Writing Instrument Industry (for Parker Pen), 1967 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-61-ABC. Businessmen's Attitudes Toward Motels, 1967 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-62-ABC. Dr. Scholl's: Data Concerning the Foot Care Market, 1967 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-63-ABC. Midwest Bank Cards, 1967 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-64. Presentation for First Card of First National Bank of Chicago, 1967 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-65-ABC. Sears Merchandise Evaluation, 1967 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-65.1-A. Presentation for Scholl Manufacturing, 1967 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-66. Soup Fact Book, 1968; 2 folders (Box R58)
    - X9.5-66.1-ABC. Summary of Expansion Markets for Campbell's V-8, 1968 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-67-A. Kentucky Fried Chicken, 1968 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-68. Kentucky Fried Chicken Image and Use Patterns, 1968 (Box R58)
    - X9.5-69-A. Kentucky Fried Chicken, 1968 (Box R59)
    - X9.5-70-ABC. Coleman Company: Camping Attitudes and Practices, 1969 (Box R59)
    - X9.5-72-B. Presentation for Blue Cross & Blue Shield, 1969 (Box R59)
    - X9.5-72.1-A. Royalcote Attitudinal Research, 1970 (Box R59)
    - X9.5-73-ABC. Corporate Communications, 1971 (Box R59)
    - X9.5-74-A. The Toy Industry, 1970; 2 folders (Box R59)
    - X9.5-75-ABC. Toy Summary, 1970 (Box R59)
    - X9.5-75.1-A. Masonite Corporation: National Study on Wall Paneling, 1971 (Box R59)
    - X9.5-76-ABC. Corporate Communications, 1971 (Box R59)
    - X9.5-77-ABC. Frozen Foods: Italian, 1971 (Box R60)
    - X9.5-78-ABC. Margarine and Butter Markets in the U.S., 1971 (Box R60)
    - X9.5-79-ABC. Corporate Communications, 1971 (Box R60)
    - X9.5-79.1-A. Lux Presentation, 1971 (Box R60)
    - X9.5-80-ABC. Kemper Insurance, 1971 (Box R60)
    - X9.5-81-ABC. Masonite: Review of Hardboard Industry, 1971 (Box R60)
    - X9.5-82-B. Household Finance Corporation and the Personal Finance Industry, 1972 (Box R60)
    - X9.5-83-A. Masonite Presentation, 1972 (Box R60)
    - X9.5-84-AB. Domestic Tire Industry, undated; 2 folders (Box R60)
    - X9.5-85-AB. Wilson Sporting Goods, 1972; 2 folders (Box R61)
    - X9.5-85.1-A. Abbott Laboratories Presentation, 1972 (Box R61)
    - X9.5-86-A. Wilson Sporting Goods, 1972 (Box R61)
    - X9.5-87-A. Booth Fisheries Presentation, 1973 (Box R61)
    - X9.5-87.01-A. Hunt-Wesson Foods: Response to Questionnaire, 1974 (Box R61)
    - X9.5-87.1-A. Miles Laboratories (SOS soap pads) Presentation, 1974 (Box R61)
    - X9.5-87.2-AB. Background on the Lottery Business, 1974 (Box R61)
    - X9.5-88-A. Airline Industry, 1974; 2 folders (Box R61)
    - X9.5-88-extra. Major Advertisers Reported by JWT Eastern and Western Divisions, 1976 (Box R61)
    - X9.5-88.1-AB. Pizza Hut, 1975 (Box R61)
    - X9.5-88.4-A. JWT and the U.S. Marine Corps, 1976 (Box R62)
    - X9.5-88.5. U.S. Marine Corps Proposal, 1976; 3 folders (Box R62)
    - X9.5-89-ABC. Major Advertisers Reported by JWT Eastern and Western Divisions, 1976 (Box R62)
    - X9.5-90-A. Hunt-Wesson Foods: Response to Questionnaire, 1976 (Box R62)
    - X9.5-90.1. Hunt-Wesson Foods, 1974; 2 folders (Box R62)
    - X9.5-90.1. Hunt-Wesson Foods, 1974 (Box R63)
    - X9.5-90.2-A. Skillet Dinners Fact Book, undated (Box R63)
    - X9.5-91-A. Bekins Company, 1976 (Box R63)
    - X9.5-92-ABC. A Look at JWT Chicago, 1976 (Box R63)
    - X9.5-93-A. Hardee's: Response to Questionnaire, 1975 (Box R63)
    - X9.5-94-A. U.S. New Business Prospect Book, 1977 (Box R63)
    - X9.5-95-ABC. Quasar Strategic Research, 1977 (Box R63)
    - X9.5-95.1-A. Television Dealer Research, 1977 (Box R63)
    - X9.5-96-A. Quasar Presentation, 1977 (Box R63)
    - X9.5-97-A. Quasar Presentation, undated (Box R63)
    - X9.5-98-ABC. Baxter Travenol Laboratories, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-99-ABC. M&M Mars New Product Development, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-100-AB. Sara Lee Briefing, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-101-ABC. Selected Food Companies as Potential New Business Prospects, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-102-AB. M&M Mars New Product Development, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-103-ABC. M&M Mars New Product Overview, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-104-ABC. Colgate-Palmolive, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-105-A. American Dairy Association 1978 Food Service Marketing Plan, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-106-AB. A Look at JWT Chicago, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-107-ABC. Pabst Brewing Research, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-108-ABC. Premium Beer Brand Definition Study, 1977 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-109-A. Anheuser-Busch Presentation Planning, 1978 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-110-ABC. Royal Crown Companies, 1978 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-111-A. U.S. Marine Corps Recruitment Advertising Plan, 1978 (Box R64)
    - X9.5-111-A. U.S. Marine Corps Recruitment Advertising Plan, 1978 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-112-ABC. U.S. Marine Corps Strategic Research Review, 1978; 2 folders (Box R65)
    - X9.5-113-ABC. U.S. Marine Corps Key Target Market Motivations, 1978 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-114-A. Libby McNeil & Libby Briefing, 1978 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-115-ABC. Frito-Lay Snack Food Overview, 1978 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-116-A. U.S. Marine Corps, 1978 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-117-ABC. USDA FNS Proposal, 1978 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-117.1-A. Chevron Public Relations Proposal, 1978 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-118-ABC. Frito-Lay Program Environment Presentation, 1979 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-119-ABC. Wilson Sporting Goods, 1979 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-119.1-AB. Sporting Goods/Leisure Industry Market Review, 1979 (Box R65)
    - X9.5-120-ABC. United Airlines, 1979 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-121-ABC. Amana Refrigeration, 1979 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-121.1-A. Bahlsen of America, 1979 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-122-ABC. Hallmark Greeting Cards, 1979 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-123-ABC. Mars Inc. Focus Group, 1979 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-124-ABC. JWT Chicago Profile, undated (Box R66)
    - X9.5-125-ABC. Sheffield's O2 Proposal, 1979 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-126-ABC. Schwinn Bicycle Company, 1980 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-127-ABC. Overview of Retail Shoe Industry, 1980 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-128-ABC. ON TV: Awareness and Attitude Study, 1980 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-129-ABC. ON TV: Awareness and Attitude Study, 1980 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-130-ABC. ON TV Research, 1980 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-130.01-A. Nabisco Snack Foods Segmentation Study, 1981 (Box R66)
    - X9.5-130.1-AB. Pearle Vision Centers, 1981; 2 folders (Box R66)
    - X9.5-130.2-A. Payless Shoesource, 1981 (Box R67)
    - X9.5-130.3-A. 7-Eleven (Southland Corporation) National Penetration, 1981 (Box R67)
    - X9.5-130.5-AB. Pearle Vision Center Strategic Study, 1981 (Box R67)
    - X9.5-130.6-A. Pearle Vision Center Presentation, 1981 (Box R67)
    - X9.5-131-AB. Hallmark Greeting Cards, 1981 (Box R67)
    - X9.5-131.1-A. Steak & Ale Restaurants, 1981; 2 folders (Box R67)
    - X9.5-131.2-A. Home Electronics Video Market, undated (Box R67)
    - X9.5-131.3-A. Zenith Electronics, undated (Box R67)
    - X9.5-131.5-A. Color Television Attitude Study, undated; 2 folders (Box R67)
    - X9.5-132-ABC. Consumer Attitudes and Behavior Toward Video Cassette Recorders, 1982 (Box R68)
    - X9.5-132.1-A. Bedding Industry Opportunities for JWT Chicago, 1982 (Box R68)